Contact

rsloane1@cox.net

www.linkedin.com/in/rayna-sloane-msn-agacnp-bc-ccrn-4436459 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care

ICU

Healthcare

Certifications

Adult-Gerontological Acute Care Nurse Practitioner-AGACNP-BC

Advanced Practice Registered Nurse

CCRN

FCCS-Fundamentals of Critical Care Support

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Honors-Awards

Contribution to the Profession-2016 Nurse's Week Award

CERN-Clinical Expert Registered Nurse-2015

4 time Daisy Award Nominee

Publications

Dear Diary: I Know What You Did While in the ICU

The Utilization of Chlorhexidine Gluconate in the Bathing Practice of ICU Patients -Nursing Research

Rayna Sloane, MSN, AGACNP-BC, CCRN

Acute Care Nurse Practitioner at Sound Physicians- Hospitalist NP Phoenix, Arizona

Summary

Dedicated Acute Care Nurse Practitioner recognized for extensive experience in cardiovascular and caring for complex critical care patients in high-acuity medical centers. Demonstrates expertise in the areas of Mechanical Circulatory Support and served as an ECMO specialist, VAD specialist, Impella certified, and experienced with Tandem Heart, IABP, and other cardiac devices.

Obtained numerous awards and kudos for exceptional performance by going above and beyond to address concerns and provide exceptional patient care.

I am an acute care nurse practitioner who is board-certified with American Nurses Credentialing Center as an AGACNP-BC in addition to holding a national certification of CCRN through the American Association of Critical Care Nurses.

Experience

Sound Physicians
Acute Care Nurse Practitioner
June 2020 - Present (1 month)
Phoenix, Arizona, United States

Aya Healthcare Critical Care NP for COVID-19 assignment April 2020 - June 2020 (3 months) Bethesda, Maryland, United States

Critical Care NP on assignment to help with COVID-19 hit areas.

Dignity Health

MCS Nurse Practitioner-St. Joseph's Hospital and Medical Center Norton Thoracic Institute

October 2018 - February 2020 (1 year 5 months)

Phoenix, Arizona Area

Provides direct care as an NP for the MCS Services and Advanced Heart Failure patients pre and post-VAD implants as a part of our Mechanical Circulator Support (MCS) Program in collaboration with a multidisciplinary health care team, performs physical examinations, confers with patients in person and by phone/electronically, collaborates with others in the department to assure smooth flow of patient care consistent with established quality indicators and participates in the overall coordination of patient care. The main focus is on the care of the adult patient requiring a VAD for bridge to transplant and destination therapy across the continuum of care. Also conduct independent clinic with VAD (pre and post-implant) patients and support the physician as needed working with cardiac surgeons and advanced heart failure cardiologists.

Banner - University Medical Center 19 years 6 months

Critical Care RN V January 2011 - October 2018 (7 years 10 months) Phoenix, Arizona Area

Specialize in taking care of immediate open heart patient population and including Mechanical Circulatory Support such as VADs, IABP, Impellas, and Total Artificial Heart to name a few at our top ranked heart care hospital in the Banner System. Trained in CRRT and I am an ECMO specialist.

Certified Anesthesia Technolologist May 2003 - December 2010 (7 years 8 months) Phoenix, Arizona Area

Certified Pharmacy Technician May 1999 - April 2003 (4 years)

Grand Canyon University
Adjunct Clinical Instructor
February 2017 - March 2018 (1 year 2 months)
Phoenix, Arizona Area

Adjunct Clinical Instructor for pre-licensure RN to BSN students in Complex Care. This included rotations in critical care, ED, special procedures and step-down units. Responsibilities included: grading assignments, discussion of case studies, reviewing each student's patient/nurse assignments, simulation labs and more as outlined by the College of Nursing at GCU.

Education

Grand Canyon University

Master of Science in Nursing (MSN), Acute Care Nurse

Practitioner · (2015 - 2018)

Grand Canyon University
RN to BSN, Nursing · (2013 - 2015)

Gateway Community College
AAS in Nursing, Nursing (2008 - 2010)